export const decks = [
    {
        _id: 1,
        name: 'japanese colors',
        picture: '',
        user: 'atreides095',
        tags: ['japanese', 'colors', 'beginner'],
        cards: [
            {
                _id: '1-1',
                front: '青い',
                back: 'blue/green',
            },

            {
                _id: '1-2',
                front: '赤い',
                back: 'red',
            },
            {
                _id: '1-3',
                front: '黒い',
                back: 'black',
            },
            {
                _id: '1-4',
                front: '白い',
                back: 'white',
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        _id: 2,
        name: 'spanish colors',
        picture: '',
        user: 'atreides095',
        tags: ['japanese', 'colors', 'beginner'],
        cards: [
            {
                _id: '2-1',
                front: 'azul',
                back: 'blue',
            },

            {
                _id: '2-2',
                front: 'rojo',
                back: 'red',
            },
            {
                _id: '1-3',
                front: 'negro',
                back: 'black',
            },
            {
                _id: '1-4',
                front: 'blanco',
                back: 'white',
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        _id: 3,
        name: 'spanish days of the week',
        picture: '',
        user: 'atreides095',
        tags: ['japanese', 'colors', 'beginner'],
        cards: [
            {
                _id: '3-1',
                front: 'lunes',
                back: 'monday',
            },

            {
                _id: '3-2',
                front: 'martes',
                back: 'tuesday',
            },
            {
                _id: '3-3',
                front: 'miércoles',
                back: 'wednesday',
            },
            {
                _id: '3-4',
                front: 'jueves',
                back: 'thursday',
            },
            {
                _id: '3-5',
                front: 'viernes',
                back: 'friday',
            },
        ],
    },
];
